Finding Aid for Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.) records, 1925-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Campers files 1925-1967
  - Chronological 1925-1967
    - 1963
      - Davenport, Bruce Talmon Jr. (Box 22)
      - Doucette, William H. "Bill" (Box 22)
      - English, Jeffrey Shaw (Box 22)
      - Ford, Frederick Clifford "Freddy" (Box 22)
      - Gray, William Schuyler "Bill" Jr. (Box 22)
      - Harbaugh, Jack Eugene (Box 22)
      - Heckenkamp, William James "Bill" (Box 22)
      - Henle, John (includes James "Jim") (1963-1966) (Box 22)
      - Hersey, Randolph "Randy" (Box 22)
      - Higbie, Carlton Milo "CM" (includes Harry Quinn) (Box 22)
      - Hobson, David Brian "Davie" (Box 22)
      - Hudson, Joseph Lowthian "Fourie" (Box 22)
      - Iglehart, Austin Scott (Box 22)
      - Kline, James Peirsol (includes William Lacey) (Box 22)
      - Knight, John Lamberson "Johnny" (Box 22)
      - Kretzschmar, William A. "Bill" (Box 22)
      - Kudner, John McKone (Box 22)
      - Kyprie, Paul Marco (Box 22)
      - Lent, John DeWitt (includes William G. "Bill") (1966-1967) (Box 22)
      - Mac Nichol, David Carter "Carter" (Box 22)
      - Marshall, Geoffrey S. (Box 22)
      - Matthews, John Michael (includes Darwin Crawford "Dar") (Box 22)
      - McKinley, John R. III (Box 22)
      - McKone, William Page "Bill" (Box 22)
      - Merritt, Thomas Elliott "Tom" (Box 22)
      - Monro, Michael Alan "Mike" (Box 22)
      - Morris, John Henderson (Box 22)
      - Nassif, Ronald Floyd (Box 22)
      - North, William Harrison "Bill" (Box 22)
      - Reith, Charles C. (Box 22)
      - Robles, David Neal "Dave" Jr. (Box 22)
      - Rorick, Marvin H. "Marv" (Box 22)
      - Simmons, Douglas J., Jr. "Chip" (Box 22)
      - Smith, Stephen H. "Steve" (Box 22)
      - Umpleby, Michael Scott "Mike" (Box 22)
      - Trimble, Thomas Hart "Hart" (Box 22)
      - Valade, Christopher Carhartt "Chris" (includes Mark Robert) (1963-1965) (Box 22)
      - Wehle, J. Kent "Kent" (includes James A. "Jim") (1963-1964) (Box 22)
      - Weiss, Douglas Arthur "Doug" (Box 22)
      - Wiesel, Tom (Box 22)
    - 1964
      [Restricted until January 1 2064 ]
      - Abraham, Richard Arnold "Ricky" (Box 22)
      - Arbaugh, Steven Lee "Steve" (Box 22)
      - Beattie, Scott Mallon (Box 22)
      - Biedermann, Brent Taylor (Box 22)
      - Berlin, David Nelson "Dave" (Box 22)
      - Black, Coit A. (includes John D.) (Box 22)
      - Dye, Billy (includes David F. "Dave") (Box 22)
      - Field, Whitney K. "Whit" (Box 22)
      - Fowler, William Earl "Bill" (Box 22)
      - Glaenzer, Thomas Adams "Tom" (Box 22)
      - Gorman, Maurice P. (includes Mark J.) (Box 22)
      - Goss, Roger A. "Rog" (Box 22)
      - Gracie, William Harris "Chipper" (Box 22)
      - Griffin, Peter Raymond "Pete" (Box 22)
      - Hammond, Edmund James "Jim" (Box 22)
      - Harris, William W. "Billy" (Box 22)
      - Hoke, David Ault (includes Karl Humphreys) (Box 22)
      - Holmes, Jeffrey Alan "Jeff" (Box 22)
      - Knorr, Frederick August "Butch" (Box 22)
      - Mahoney, R. Michael "Mike" (Includes J. Patrick "Pat") (Box 22)
      - Mills, Steven Edward (Box 22)
      - Nutter, Robert Kennedy "Bob" (Box 22)
      - Rorick, Robert Baker "Rocky" (Box 22)
      - Schafer, Bruce Lee "Brucie" (includes Robert Samuel "Bobby" (1964-1965) (Box 22)
      - Sherbondy, David Edwin "Dave" (Box 22)
      - Stutt, James Valley "Jamie" (Box 22)
      - Tatum, Christopher Lee "Chris" (Box 22)
      - Wardwell, Jeffrey Holbrook "Jeff" (Box 22)
      - Winchester, Alan Weeks, Jr. "Wix" (Box 22)
    - 1965
      [Restricted until January 1 2065 ]
      - Anderson, Eric Worden (Box 23)
      - Athey, Robert L. "Bobby" (includes Brian David) (Box 23)
      - Bassett, Joseph D. Bassett "Joe" (includes Robert O. "Rob") (Box 23)
      - Batsch, Charles Warren "Chuck" (Box 23)
      - Binford, Wilson Clark "Bill" (Box 23)
      - Chilcote, Thomas Jones "Tommy" (Box 23)
      - Christman, Thomas Robert "Tom" (Box 23)
      - Corbridge, Charles Kelley "Kel" (includes Robert Scott "Scotty") (Box 23)
      - Dickey, Mathew "Mat" (Box 23)
      - Eurich, Donald (Box 23)
      - Field, Steven Alan "Steve" (Box 23)
      - Fitzgerald, Richard Michael "Mike" (Box 23)
      - Flannery, Michael Rogers "Mike" (Box 23)
      - Hall, Donald Andrew III "Andrew" (Box 23)
      - Harrison, Richard Lawrence "Dick" (Box 23)
      - Holiday, Harry III "Hap" (Box 23)
      - Jensen, James Crawford "Jim" (Box 23)
      - Mason, Horatio Pleasants "Pete" (Box 23)
      - Miller, Jonathon Paul (Box 23)
      - Moxley, Cameron "Cammy" (Box 23)
      - Phillips, David Chaffee "Dave" (Box 23)
      - Reilly, William Carlson "Billy" (includes Richard Cating "Richie") (1965-1966) (Box 23)
      - Richards, John W. "John" (Box 23)
      - Rosenberg, Jonathan "Jon" (Box 23)
      - Tucker, Lance Christopher "Butch" (Box 23)
      - Wallaert, Albert Jay "Beanie" (Box 23)
      - Weed, Cornelius C. III "Neal" (Box 23)
      - Woodward, James Hanna "Woody" (Box 23)
    - 1966
      [Restricted until January 1 2066 ]
      - Alzamora, Victor A. "Tito" (Box 23)
      - Beardsley, Charles Harold II "Chip" (Box 23)
      - Camp, David Lee "Dave" (Box 23)
      - Carroll, Charles H. "Chip" (Box 23)
      - Cavill, Bruce Dean (Box 23)
      - Christensen, James Robert "Jim" (Box 23)
      - Cobb, Brian Edward (Box 23)
      - Conaghan, Mark Thomas (Box 23)
      - Conibear, Michael "Mike" (Box 23)
      - deKam, Peter Fredrik (Box 23)
      - Dukay, Victor (Box 23)
      - Dyson, Alfred Leonard III "Chip" (includes David McDaniel "Dave") (Box 23)
      - Edwards, Stevenson L. "Steve" (includes Wade R.) (1964-1965) (Box 23)
      - Ely, Bartlett Spalding "Bart" (Box 23)
      - Garwood, Terry Anderson "Shades" (Box 23)
      - Gedrich, Daniel Michael "Dan" (Box 23)
      - Hall, Charles Louis "Charley" (Box 23)
      - Haugen, Mark Pell (Box 23)
      - Hickey, Michael Thomas "Mike" (Box 23)
      - Hopkins, William Robert "Bill" (includes Neil Colin) (Box 23)
      - Johnson, Scott William "Crusher" (Box 23)
      - Keeney, Timothy Val "Tim" (Box 23)
      - Moore, Dale Logan (Box 23)
      - Osler, Peter Lorch (Box 23)
      - Raymond, Randall James "Randy" (Box 23)
      - Schuman, Charles Lewis "Chuck" (Box 23)
      - Sharp, Jeffrey G. "Jeff" (Box 23)
      - Starrett, David Blake "Dave" (Box 23)
      - Templeton, Richard Scott "Scott" (Box 23)
      - Tomlin, John Grant "Grant" (Box 23)
      - Waldron, Scott Douglas (Box 23)
      - Wendahl, Eric Friend (Box 23)
    - 1967
      [Restricted until January 1 2067 ]
      - Andrews, Frank M. III, "Skip" (Box 23)
      - Ankenbruck, James Matthew "Matt" (Box 23)
      - Brown, John Randell (includes Peter Burke "Pete") (Box 23)
      - Cooley, Brad (Box 23)
      - Correil, Jonathan H. "Jon" (Box 23)
      - Cowing, James A. "Jim" (Box 23)
      - Drake, William D. "Chuck" (Box 23)
      - Early, Ellis Terrill III "Terry" (Box 23)
      - Ford, James W. "Jim" (Box 23)
      - Gust, Rockwell T. "Rocky" (Box 23)
      - Helm, David Leroy "Dave" (Box 23)
      - Helmke, Louis Edmund (Box 23)
      - Hodge, Arthur Wilton "Art" (Box 23)
      - Judge, Paul Cordiner (Box 23)
      - Katz, David Frank "Dave" (Box 23)
      - Kirkland, "Skip" (Box 23)
      - Lombard, David Carleton (Box 23)
      - Macartney, Grant Street (Box 23)
      - Marr, Richard A. "Ricky" (Box 23)
      - McKelvy, C. Lockhart "Lock" (Box 23)
      - Miller, Robert C. "Bob" (Box 23)
      - Murphy, Bill (Box 23)
      - Olson, David Lee "Dave" (includes Kent Roger) (Box 23)
      - Osler, Peter L. "Pete" (Box 23)
      - Peppel, Paul Karl (Box 23)
      - Petropoulos, John G. (Box 23)
      - Premo, Edward F. "Ed" (Box 23)
      - Reye, Gary George (Box 23)
      - Reynolds, Sherman Joseph (Box 23)
      - Rogge, William Fisher Jr., "Bill" (Box 23)
      - Schneider, Christopher Duane "Chris" (includes Mark Cowing) (Box 23)
      - Skakel, Rushton W. "Ricky" (Box 23)
      - Slotfeldt, Per (Box 23)
      - Stirling, Jamie (Box 23)
      - Storrs, John A. (Box 23)
      - Turner, William Ford "Bill" (Box 23)
      - Valade, Mark R. (Box 23)
      - Vaughn, Tad M. (includes Rex R.) (Box 23)
      - Weber, Mark Alexander (Box 23)
      - Weisman, Bruce Meyer (Box 23)
      - Wohlgemuth, Edward W. Jr. "Ted" (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1967 (Box 23)
    - Alumni Association Update Cards (Box 23)
  - Alphabetical File. 1925-1960
    - Acklin, Evan Callord (1938) (Box 23)
    - Allmand, Thomas Robert "Tommy" (1949) (Box 23)
    - Anderson, Pehr Denton (includes John Albin) (1945) (Box 23)
    - Ayres, Byron (1935) (Box 23)
    - Bandfield, David G. (1944) (Box 23)
    - Belser, Martin Fisk "Marty" (1942 1949) (Box 23)
    - Biggs, Raymond John "Ray" (includes Thomas William "Tom") (1946-1949) (Box 23)
    - Bird, Mrs. Iris (1947) (Box 23)
    - Bracken, Frank A. (1947) (Box 23)
    - Braheney, Thomas Jerome (1938) (Box 23)
    - Brigham, Brian P. (1949) (Box 23)
    - Bryan, Rodney "Rod" (1948-1949) (Box 23)
    - Bull, Richard (includes Robert) (1946) (Box 23)
    - Buszek, Beatrice R. (1947) (Box 23)
    - Butterfield, James (1946) (Box 23)
    - Card, Robert Watson "Robin" (1949) (Box 23)
    - Coan, Peter Gaylord (1946) (Box 23)
    - Copelin, Carl Brown "Brownie" (1944-1949) (Box 23)
    - Cost, John Joseph, Jr. (1945) (Box 23)
    - Courtis, William Stuart "Bill" (1947-1949) (Box 23)
    - Cress, George Henry (1944) (Box 23)
    - Cudlip, Robert Sherwood "Jack" (1934-1939) (Box 23)
    - Curtis, James Christie (1946) (Box 23)
    - Curtis, Charles (includes Philip) (1943-1944) (Box 23)
    - Davis, Thomas Eugene "Tom" (1949) (Box 23)
    - Dettlinger, Frederick W., Jr. (1946) (Box 23)
    - DeVore, Richard S. "Dick" (includes Robert William "Bob") (1949) (Box 23)
    - Doan, L. Alden (includes Herbert D. "Ted") (1929-1935) (Box 23)
    - Dobson, Rusty (1953) (Box 24)
    - Dobson, Stephen Boyd "Steve" (includes Peter MacLaunn) (1958-1960) (Box 24)
    - Douglas, Donald O. II (1944) (Box 24)
    - Dreese, Richard Nadeau "Dick" (1938-1939) (Box 24)
    - Dryden, George Eastman, Jr. (1938-1942) (Box 24)
    - Durst, Raymond (1944) (Box 24)
    - Ehman, Thomas F. "Tom" (1948-1949) (Box 24)
    - Elliott, Richard (1935-1936) (Box 24)
    - Fischer, Patrick Carl (1946) (Box 24)
    - Flesh, Alexander Smith (1938-1943) (Box 24)
    - Foster, Lawrence T. "Larry" (1946-1949) (Box 24)
    - Gabel, Norman W. (1946) (Box 24)
    - Garvey, Robert Arthur (1938-1939) (Box 24)
    - Giannestras, James Duncan "Jim" (1947-1949) (Box 24)
    - Goodwillie, Scott (deceased) (1928) (Box 24)
    - Gundrum, Frederick "Skipper" (1948-1949) (Box 24)
    - Hars, Ritz (1938-1942) (Box 24)
    - Herman, Donald Allen "Don" (1948-1949) (Box 24)
    - Higgins, Linnaes Boyd (1935-1947) (Box 24)
    - Hooper, Joe (1942) (Box 24)
    - Houck, Lawrence B. (1946-1950) (Box 24)
    - Igleheart, Edgar, Jr. (1934) (Box 24)
    - Irish, Jim (1953) (Box 24)
    - Irvin, Charles E. (1945-1946) (Box 24)
    - Jelliffe, Jack Hare (1938-1945) (Box 24)
    - Keely, Billy M. (1946) (Box 24)
    - Kern, Ernst Frederick, Jr. (Fritz) (1949) (Box 24)
    - Kirstein, Bob (1928) (Box 24)
    - Kretzschmar, Bob (1942) (Box 24)
    - Landen, Joseph D. (1938-1942) (Box 24)
    - Lathrop, Walter William, Jr. (1945) (Box 24)
    - Leckie, Major G. (1946) (Box 24)
    - Lighty, Jack D. (1942-1949) (Box 24)
    - Lyons, Laurance Alden (1945) (Box 24)
    - Mackey, Thomas Abbott (1946-1951) (Box 24)
    - Malcolm, Peter (includes James) (1946) (Box 24)
    - Marin, Edwin Woodruff (1948-1954) (Box 24)
    - Marquette, Eugene Oakleigh III (1947-1951) (Box 24)
    - Marquette, Joseph Chartrand (1948-1949) (Box 24)
    - Marr, Richard Austin (includes Walter Durant) (1940-1952) (Box 24)
    - Matuszewski, Edward (1948-1952) (Box 24)
    - Milburn, Joseph Andrews "Joe" (1945-1949) (Box 24)
    - Miller, George William (includes James Mann, Jr.) (1944-1950) (Box 24)
    - Moore, Joseph Edward "Joe" (1948-1949) (Box 24)
    - Mott, Stewart R. "Stew" (1949) (Box 24)
    - Mumma, Roger K. "Rog" (1948-1949) (Box 24)
    - Newberry, Charles Milton (1938-1939) (Box 24)
    - Nielsen, Philip P. "Phil" (1946-1949) (Box 24)
    - Nilsen, Christopher "Chris" (includes Nicholas "Nick") (1946-1949) (Box 24)
    - Noble, Bruce Jack (1943-1945) (Box 24)
    - Nolan, John Jeremiah "Jerry" (1938-1943) (Box 24)
    - Nolan, Robert Leslie (1938) (Box 24)
    - Palmer, Nathan H. (includes Bradley H.) (1946) (Box 24)
    - Paulson, Peter Joseph (includes LeRoy Thomas) (1945-1947) (Box 24)
    - Pierce, Richard (1946) (Box 24)
    - Pilliod, Thomas Jack (1945-1946) (Box 24)
    - Ratliff, Berry (1955) (Box 24)
    - Raymond, John Stowell (1947) (Box 24)
    - Reed, Dan Dwight (1948-1949) (Box 24)
    - Richardson, Ross C. (1948-1949) (Box 24)
    - Roth, Philip James M. (1944) (Box 24)
    - Sawicki, Ralph (1948-1953) (Box 24)
    - Scher, Stephen (1947-1948) (Box 24)
    - Schively, Nicholson Roots "Nick" (1938-1939) (Box 24)
    - Schott, Kenneth Crittenden (1945) (Box 24)
    - Seacrest, Jimmie (1947) (Box 24)
    - Severs, Roy M. (1946) (Box 24)
    - Silkworth, Donald (1947-1953) (Box 24)
    - Stienon, Francis Michael (includes Julian Peter) (1947-1950) (Box 24)
    - Strickler, William J. "Billy" (1949) (Box 24)
    - Stroh, Edwin R. III "Bill" (includes Peter B.) (1958-1959) (Box 24)
    - Talbot, Gerald J. (includes George-cousin) (1946) (Box 24)
    - Telfer, G. Thomas (1948) (Box 24)
    - Tieteg, Larry (1956) (Box 24)
    - Tolfree, Daniel Eugene (1944) (Box 24)
    - Tomblin, Gale Edward (1947-1949) (Box 24)
    - Twining, William F. "Bill" (1939) (Box 24)
    - VanderVeen, John David "Dave" (1947-1949) (Box 24)
    - Vos, John F. (1948-1954) (Box 24)
    - Wagner, Albert W. "Sandy" (1944) (Box 24)
    - Warren, John (includes Pat) (1948) (Box 24)
    - Weber, Tom W. (includes Carl R.) (1946-1953) (Box 24)
    - White, Benjamin Baily, III (1947) (Box 24)
    - Whitman, Peter Depew "Pete" (1945-1949) (Box 24)
    - Willertz, Frederick "Freddy" (1948-1951) (Box 24)
    - Williams, John Russell (1944-1952) (Box 24)
    - Yaryan, John Sturges, Jr. (1944-1948) (Box 24)
- Staff / Counselors files
  - Alphabetical 1925-1959
    - Albert, Dr. & Mrs. Richard & Catherine (1948) (Box 25)
    - Allison, Paul (1927) (Box 25)
    - Anderson, Mr. Louis J. (1931-1933) (Box 25)
    - Andrews, Tom (1945) (Box 25)
    - Barrett, David Joseph (1949) (Box 25)
    - Baske, Dr. Franklin W. (1929) (Box 25)
    - Beal, Mr. Robert (1930) (Box 25)
    - Beierlein, Dr. Karl (1926) (Box 25)
    - Bennett, Mr. Dick (1926-1927) (Box 25)
    - Benson, John (1936) (Box 25)
    - Berndt, Mr. Arnold W. (1929) (Box 25)
    - Binford, Tom, Junior Counselor, (1941) (Box 25)
    - Bittinger, Mr. Ross T. (1928-1932) (Box 25)
    - Blake, Forrester (1935) (Box 25)
    - Blocksma, Douglas (1939) (Box 25)
    - Blomfield, Lloyd (1935) (Box 25)
    - Boden, Mr. Marshall (1928) (Box 25)
    - Boehringer, Mr. Albert (1926) (Box 25)
    - Braidwood, Van (1945) (Box 25)
    - Brashares, Charles Merrill (1937) (Box 25)
    - Browne, Dr. Trevor G. (1926-1931) (Box 25)
    - Bryan, Christy A. (1947) (Box 25)
    - Bryan, Don (1948) (Box 25)
    - Bryan, Taylor (1946) (Box 25)
    - Bryant, Jim (1941) (Box 25)
    - Buchanan, Mr. Walter (1931) (Box 25)
    - Buckmaster, Clifford (1943) (Box 25)
    - Burow, George E. (1941) (Box 25)
    - Buszek, Ted C. (1947) (Box 25)
    - Campbell, C. Marsh (1949) (Box 25)
    - Cantrill, Mr. Cecil, Jr. (1929-1930) (Box 25)
    - Carter, Mr. Clare "Newt" (1925-1931) (Box 25)
    - Cathcart, Dr. Edward (1928) (Box 25)
    - Chubb, Donald (1945) (Box 25)
    - Conlin, Mr. Joseph (1929-1932) (Box 25)
    - Coon, Jim (1947) (Box 25)
    - Cooper, Dr. Ralph (1940) (Box 25)
    - Cooper, Dr. Robert (1927) (Box 25)
    - Corbett, Mr. Thad (1928-1931) (Box 25)
    - Corrigan, Clare (1944) (Box 25)
    - Courville, Dr. Charles J. (1939) (Box 25)
    - Crandall, Frank, Jr. (1949) (Box 25)
    - Cunningham, Mr. C. Howard (1931) (Box 25)
    - Daniells, Mr. William (1930-1932) (Box 25)
    - Deacon, Wallace (1943) (Box 25)
    - Dennison, Ed (1945) (Box 25)
    - Der Derian, Arthur (1946) (Box 25)
    - De Tar, Jack (1942) (Box 25)
    - De Vinney, Leland (1935) (Box 25)
    - Doherty, Mr. J. Kenneth (1935) (Box 25)
    - Donahue, Carl (1933-1934) (Box 25)
    - Doty, Mr. Alfred E. (1930) (Box 25)
    - Dutton, Fred (1949) (Box 25)
    - Eckardt, Mr. Bowne (1928-1929) (Box 25)
    - Edwards, Lee H. (1948) (Box 25)
    - English, Gene (1945) (Box 25)
    - English, Robert (1942) (Box 25)
    - Ericsson, Samuel S. (1941) (Box 25)
    - Ernst, Fred (1941) (Box 25)
    - Espeland, Mr. Nels (1930-1932) (Box 25)
    - Evenson, Mr. Clarence O. (1929-1931) (Box 25)
    - Farrior, Dr. Brown (1939) (Box 25)
    - Farrior, Dr. Robert (1934) (Box 25)
    - Feldkamp, Mr. Rolland (1928-1929) (Box 25)
    - Ferguson, Allyn C. (1941) (Box 25)
    - Ferrin, Harvey M. (1934) (Box 25)
    - Flinchpaugh, Mr. James (1930-1933) (Box 25)
    - Follis, William (1938) (Box 25)
    - Freeman, Don (1929-1930) (Box 25)
    - Freyberg, Dick (1926-1931) (Box 25)
    - Fries, Charles (1942) (Box 25)
    - Fry, Bill (1944) (Box 25)
    - Fultz, Keith (1948) (Box 25)
    - Gabel, Mr. Walter (1925) [deceased 1929] (Box 25)
    - Gaddis, Edwin A. (1944) (Box 25)
    - Gaddis, Shirley (1943) (Box 25)
    - Gandall, Mr. John (1930) (Box 25)
    - Garlinghouse, Bruce (1942) (Box 25)
    - Garrett, Bob (1947) (Box 25)
    - Geil, Russell (1933-1934) (Box 25)
    - Genebach, Larry (1942) (Box 25)
    - George, Mr. Henry (1928-1930) (Box 25)
    - George, John (1938) [junior staff] (Box 25)
    - Gibbons, Mr. Sherman (1928-1931) (Box 25)
    - Goodwin, Henry S. (1932) (Box 25)
    - Grace, Mr. James D. (1931) (Box 25)
    - Graham, Garret (1946) (Box 25)
    - Granger, Ned (1940) (Box 25)
    - Gray, Dick (1948) (Box 25)
    - Gray, George F. (1933) (Box 25)
    - Gray, Mr. Harvey (1927) (Box 25)
    - Greenawalt, George (1943) (Box 25)
    - Greene, John (1944) (Box 25)
    - Gresso, Vernon (1944) (Box 25)
    - Grimm, James (1935) (Box 25)
    - Gugle, Frederick B. (1946) (Box 25)
    - Gundersen, Ralph Martin (1949) (Box 25)
    - Hacker, Dave (1943) (Box 26)
    - Hallett, Mrs. Frances (includes Tommy) (1946) (Box 26)
    - Hammond, Geo. M. D. (1941) (Box 26)
    - Hansen, Brynjulf (1946) (Box 26)
    - Harbaugh, Mr. W. D. (1929) (Box 26)
    - Harmon, Louis, 2nd Cook (1925) (Box 26)
    - Harrigan, Mr. Frank (1927-1928) (Box 26)
    - Harvey, Emerson J. (1940) (Box 26)
    - Hawkins, Mr. Harry (1925) (Box 26)
    - Helfrick, Charles K., Jr. (1935) (Box 26)
    - Heneveld, Lloyd A. (1949) (Box 26)
    - Hess, Bill (1944) (Box 26)
    - Hess, John (1943) (Box 26)
    - Higgins, William Robert, Jr. "Bill" (1949) (Box 26)
    - Hill, Dr. Theron (1927) (Box 26)
    - Hills, Charles (1947) (Box 26)
    - Hipwood, Rubee (1949) (Box 26)
    - Hokenson, Mr. Billy (1928) (Box 26)
    - Houghey, David (1936) (Box 26)
    - Hume, H. Ross (1946) (Box 26)
    - Hume, Robert H. (1946) (Box 26)
    - Hutchins, Robert (1926) [died 1927] (Box 26)
    - Ingold, John (1934) (Box 26)
    - Ivanhoff, John (1938) (Box 26)
    - Jacobson, Eric (1938) (Box 26)
    - Jerome, M. D. (1926) (Box 26)
    - Jewell, Ken (1943) (Box 26)
    - Jobe, Mr. William T. (1929) (Box 26)
    - Johnson, Edward (1941) (Box 26)
    - Johnson, Glenn (1941) (Box 26)
    - Johnson, Merlin (1945) (Box 26)
    - Johnston, Mr. Tim (1928) (Box 26)
    - Jones, Bruce DeHaven (1949) (Box 26)
    - Jones, Mr. George B. (1949) (Box 26)
    - Jones, Lloyd (1944) (Box 26)
    - Jones, Mrs. Myra (1949) (Box 26)
    - Jones, Lt. Paul W. (1935) (Box 26)
    - Jordan, John W., Jr. (1949) (Box 26)
    - Kell, Robert (1948) (Box 26)
    - Kellogg, Mr. Stanley (1931-1934) (Box 26)
    - Kent, Mr. Paul (1938) (Box 26)
    - Keppelman, Tom (1935) (Box 26)
    - Kinahan, Fred (1937) (Box 26)
    - King, Lawrence A. (1947) (Box 26)
    - Kishpaugh, Gloria D. (1944-1946) (Box 26)
    - Klein, Maynard (1933-1934) (Box 26)
    - Knechtel, Mr. Otto G. (1925) (Box 26)
    - Koceski, Leo Robert (1949) (Box 26)
    - Krause, Mr. Owen (1928-1930) (Box 26)
    - Kretzschmar, William Addison (1949) (Box 26)
    - Kroske, Carl (1949) (Box 26)
    - Lacker, Bill (1947) (Box 26)
    - La Follette, Ernest (1939) (Box 26)
    - Lane, Robert (1944) (Box 26)
    - Largent, Mr. William (1926) (Box 26)
    - Lashmet, Dr. Floyd (1930-1931) (Box 26)
    - Legault, Mr. Jack B. (1931) (Box 26)
    - Lewis, Clayton (1940) (Box 26)
    - Lickert, Mr. George (1925) (Box 26)
    - Lister, Mr. William (1931-1933) (Box 26)
    - Livingston, Mr. Glenn (1930-1931) (Box 26)
    - Loughlin, W. R. (1931) (Box 26)
    - Lovejoy, Mr. William (1927-1929) (Box 26)
    - Lowry, Mr. George, Jr. (1927-1928) (Box 26)
    - Lowry, Dr. George, Sr. (1928) (Box 26)
    - Lurkins, John (1949) (Box 26)
    - Mann, Oliver D., Jr. (1945) (Box 26)
    - Marceau, J. Edward (1935-1935), 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Marantette, Kenneth (1958) (Box 26)
    - Massey, Kenneth (1941) (Box 26)
    - Matson, Mr. George E. (1927) (Box 26)
    - Matteson, Max Richard (1948) (Box 26)
    - Matthews, David O. (1947) (Box 26)
    - Maxson, Mr. William T. (1927-1930) (Box 26)
    - Maxwell, Dr. J. H. (1930) (Box 26)
    - McCaffree, Chas., Jr. (1933) (Box 26)
    - McCaffree, Charlie "Mac" (1948) (Box 26)
    - McCall, Mr. Robert (1927) (Box 26)
    - McCoy, Mr. Ernie (1928-1932) (Box 26)
    - McCray, Sam (1936) (Box 26)
    - McDowell, James (1945) (Box 26)
    - McFadden, Mr. Bruce (1928) (Box 26)
    - McManus, Ruth (1945) (Box 26)
    - McMillan, Albert (1939) (Box 26)
    - Menzies, Clifford G. (1929-1930) (Box 26)
    - Metzler, Mr. John P. (1929-1930) (Box 26)
    - Miller, Mr. William (1932-1933) (Box 26)
    - Mitchell, Philip H. (1934) (Box 26)
    - Mithofer, Dr. James (1942) (Box 26)
    - Monteith, Mrs. L. (1939) (Box 26)
    - Moore, John C. (1932-1933) (Box 26)
    - Naugle, Gordon Paul (1948) (Box 26)
    - Nederlandon, Bill (1948) (Box 26)
    - Neitzke, Ernest (1934) (Box 26)
    - Noble, Virgil (1943) (Box 26)
    - North, Harold D., Jr. (1930) (Box 26)
    - Northrop, Mr. Phil (1925-1930) (Box 26)
    - Oetjen, Donald V. (1947) (Box 26)
    - Ortmann, Charles H. "Chuck" (1949) (Box 26)
    - Owen, William H. (1947) (Box 26)
    - Parker, Alden (1947) (Box 26)
    - Parker, Louis (1932-1933) (Box 26)
    - Patterson, Mr. Gail "Pat" (1926-1927) (Box 26)
    - Peale, Miss Ruth (1932) (Box 26)
    - Penn, Mrs. Blanche (1944) (Box 26)
    - Petty, Mr. Ross (1928-1931) (Box 26)
    - Phelps, Seth (1936) (Box 26)
    - Philbin, Mr. "Let" (1927-1929) (Box 26)
    - Plenderleith, Ian (1946) (Box 26)
    - Pulling, Mr. Albert Van S. (1930-1933) (Box 26)
    - Pursell, Lester J. (1946) (Box 26)
    - Rawson, Dr. Perry (1936) (Box 27)
    - Reed, Mr. Gerald G. (1926-1931) (Box 27)
    - Rees, Harry Jr. (1937) (Box 27)
    - Rider, Mr. T. Bruce (1926-1931) (Box 27)
    - Riecks, Donald Yale (1945) (Box 27)
    - Rifenburg, Dick (1948) (Box 27)
    - Robare, Mr. Eddie (1925-1929) (Box 27)
    - Roberts, Donald M. (1949) (Box 27)
    - Roberts, Jack (1943) (Box 27)
    - Robertson, Mr. Glen (1928-1930) (Box 27)
    - Robinson, Mr. James (1925-1930) (Box 27)
    - Robinson, James (1946) (Box 27)
    - Romanick, Mr. John (1939) (Box 27)
    - Ross, Fred (1932-1933) (Box 27)
    - Ross, Worth (1948) (Box 27)
    - Russell, Gail "Hap" (1946) (Box 27)
    - Ryan, William M. (1945) (Box 27)
    - Ryder, Joseph Frances (1941) (Box 27)
    - Schaubel, Mr. Ray (1932-1933) (Box 27)
    - Schruben, Bob (1944) (Box 27)
    - Schulz, Dick (1946) (Box 27)
    - Schupp, Jack (1945) (Box 27)
    - Searles, John (1948) (Box 27)
    - Seay, Jim (1948) (Box 27)